[Music]
foreign
I'm a wealth consultant with Prudential
Life what would I say to someone who
wants to join Prudential I'll actually
say you are actually wasting time by not
joining right now
why do I say that
um I'll share my personal experience
I lost my job three years ago and
decided to take one Prudential after
being persuaded many times to come and
join I've not looked back I've not
regretted why it gives me Liberation
so the job really offers me
flexible time with my family and in
terms of making the money I'm able to
make the money that I want to make
the flexibility of time means that I can
plan my day and be able to plan my
activities without that fixed time that
you have to be in in an office
so anybody that's looking for a job that
gives them that free time
I would say come and join us